Antonio Cuadra

WEB DEVELOPER · SYSTEM ENGINEER MAJOR

🛮 🕻 (+505) 8353-0296 | 🔀 acuadraq@gmail.com | 🏕 www.acuadraq.tech | 🖸 AlexC01 | 🛅 antonio-cuadra-quezada

Summary

Graduated student, and worked as a Web Developer for the past year. I am passionate for technologies of the front-end such as React, Gatsby and Sass, but also I am able to work on the back-end with Python and with database knowledge. Enjoys making great UI for a beautiful experience for the user, and always learning new things to accomplish goals on the best way possible.

Skills

Technical Skills HTML/CSS/Javascript · ReactJS · Typescript · GatsbyJS · PostgreSQL · Python · Django · Sass

Languages Native Spanish · Fluent in English **Art Technology** Adobe Photoshop · Adobe Premiere Pro

Work Experience _____

Kronoscode Managua, Nicaragua

Web Developer Feb. 2021 - Sep. 2021

- Developed in Diango to provide web applications on the best way possible, and also using PostgreSQL to manipulate data.
- Improved the SEO, to earn more traffic and improve the experience to the users.
- Implemented great UI, and responsive designs for a good experience.

Applaudo StudiosSan Salvador, El Salvador

REACT DEVELOPER TRAINEE Sep. 2021 - Dec. 2021

- Developed as React Trainee, learning different technologies each week.
- Implemented multiple technologies in every project, such as ReactJS, Gatsby, Typescript.
- Designed and implemented a good UI and responsive designs to each project, to have a perfect website.
- Implemented testing to mock a user experience and solve errors found by every test.

Education

UAM (American University)

Managua, Nicaragua

Bachelor of System Engineer 2017 - 2021

• Graduated as a Systems Engineer.

CERTIFICATION ON JAVASCRIPT ALGORITHMS AND DATA STRUCTURES

UAM (American University)

Manaqua, Nicaraqua

PROJECT MANAGMENT Jun. 2021 - Dec. 2021

• Created a product from scratch, and make all the way to selling the product as a company.

Freecodecamp

2021

• Learned algorithms and data structures, completing exercises and mastering each data structure.